Murtaza Kankroliwala

Software Developer

I have 3+ years of professional expertise in full stack web and app development. I am a Keen learner and love to work on any Technical Stuff and ready to learn new things on Professional as well as personal aspect. Searching for opportunities to get experience and learn new tech stacks.





mkankroli3@gmail.com



Mumbai, India



in linkedin.com/in/murtaza-kankroliwala-938514168

+91 9819542253



mkankroliportfolio.netlify.app/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Developer

LogisticsNow Pvt. Ltd.

10/2020 - Present

Mulund, Maharashtra, India

Digital Backbone of logistics to help Transporters and Manufacturers to build a technology enabled transportation and logistics business.

Work Description:

- Full Stack Developer skilled in product, architecture, and design, ensuring seamless system integration and performance.
- Developed live B2B Web and Mobile App bridging Transporters and Manufacturers, enhancing Supply Chain Logistics.
- Expertise in React and Python, leveraged Microsoft Azure tools (CosmosDB, Function Apps, SignalR, etc.) for robust application development.
- Craft UI designs, user flows with precision using Balasamiq, Figma, and draw.io.

Team Lead for Full Stack App and Web Developer Intern Upcloud Technology

04/2020 - 10/2020

Remote

Platform for Digital Healthcare Industry

Work Description

- Development of Doctor's App using Flutter and Dart for a cutting-edge and efficient tech solution.
- Designed a patient-centric web app for profile creation, appointment booking, and feedback/review system integration.
- Served as a Tech Leader, guiding a team of 4-5 individuals to successful project

Associate Software Engineer Intern

LogisticsNow

12/2019 - 03/2020

Mulund, Mumbai

86.24

Digital Backbone of logistics to help Transporters and Manufacturers to build a technology enabled transportation and logistics business.

- Built a ReactJS-powered Map webapp, showcasing proficiency in creating compact and functional location-based solutions.
- Tested web applications, provided feedback, and contributed to bug resolution, ensuring enhanced performance and user experience.

EDUCATION

B.Tech in Computer Engineering

K. J. Somaiya College of Engg., Somaiya Vidyanagar, Vidyavihar

06/2017 - 10/2020 7.89

Diploma in Computer Technology

M.M. Babasaheb Gawde Institute of Technology

08/2014 - 06/2017

SKILLS

Python

Flutter App Development

App Development

Form Recognizer

ACHIEVEMENTS

LogisticsNow: Spot Award

For Estimation and completion of work on estimated time.

3rd in Technical Paper Presentation

For TiffinVilla Project, Android App to send the tiffin from one place to another

PERSONAL PROJECTS

B.Tech Project (06/2019 - 06/2020)

Fire Extinguishing Support System for fire station where user can report the fire station using app or using IoT if Alarms the nearest Fire Station for help.

Diploma Project (06/2016 - 04/2017)

TiffinVilla: Android Application to get user the home made food.

NGO Project (01/2019 - 04/2019)

A Mini Project in Third Year Engineering.

Inventory Management (11/2020 - 01/2021)

Short App Development for Rockford's where the drivers add their stock details and maintains transfer.

CERTIFICATES/AWARDS

TiffinVilla (09/2016 - 09/2016)

3rd Prize In Paper Project Presentation

Technical Leader In CSI (06/2015 - 12/2017)

Kyrion Tech Ethical Hacking Workshop From IIT ROMBAY